[Kingdom 15 Translation by Kewl0210]
I came to take your life.
（王騎(おうき)）
あなたの命をいただきに来ました
Depending on your answer to this, that is.
あなたのお答えしだいではね
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）古代中国
Ancient China.
聖者の時代は終わりを告げ
人間の欲望は解放されていた
After learning that the era of saints had ended,
human desire was unleashed.
And a storm of violent wars erupted for 500 years...
戦乱の嵐が
500年にわたって吹き荒れ
until over one hundred states were reduced to merely seven.
100を超えた国々は
７つに淘汰(とうた)された
And now, a wind of great history gusts from the State of Qin in the far West.
そして今 西の果ての国 秦(しん)から―
大いなる歴史が
生まれようとしている
This is the tumultuous tale of a nameless boy and a young king who brought the warring era to its end!
これは
戦乱の時代を生き抜いた―
名もなき少年と若き王の
激動の物語である
（信(しん)）ンンッ！
Presented by Anime-Destiny
Translation
kewl0210
itsumo yori hayaku kietetta hoshi zora ni
いつもより早く消えてった星空に
In a starry sky that disappeared faster than it ever has
kusanariatta deai wa
重なり合った出会いは
the many piled up meetings we've had
Editing
jagman1x3
ore wo nomikonde iku
俺を呑み込んでいく
swallow me.
kono yume wa kudakenai
この夢は砕けない
This dream cannot be broken.
Timing
rtrs
sabitsukaseta kyoufushin
錆びつかせた恐怖心
Among this rusted fear in my heart
yuragu fuan no naka de
揺らぐ不安の中で
and the anxiety that makes me waver
Typesetting
rtrs
ame wo saegiru shinjitsu
雨を遮る信実
is a truth that interrupts the rain.
dare ni mo ubaeyashinai
誰にも奪えやしない
No one can take it away,
Karaoke
kewl0210
FZeroWing
onaji keshiki ni hisonda puraido
同じ景色にひそんだプライド
our pride that lurks in the same landscape.
Encode
max80
itsuka kitto kanau ima mo mieru kibou fortitude
いつかきっと叶う 今も見える希望 fortitude
The fortuitous desire I have will definitely come true one day.
yowasa wo sute wa shinai
弱さを捨てはしない
We won't throw away our weaknesses,
oretachi no kienai shiin
俺達の消えないシーン
those are scenes that won't disappear.
furenzokusen no youni hashiru kibou unbreakable heart
不連続線の様に走る希望 unbreakable heart
My desire in my unbreakable heart runs like a discontinuitous line.
I knew at the start that there's no end.
QC
Mistral[sA]
I've made up my mind, right now it's the time to take the first step.
Distro
kokus
Kittie
prefix-
Now's the only time.
～♪
Qualifications of a King
I have only one thing I'd like to ask you.
質問させていただきたいことは
ただひとつ
あなたさまは どのような王を
目指しておられます？
What kind of king do you aim to be, my lord?
じっくり考えて お答えください
Please think about it carefully before answering.
私の宝刀は
不遜な言葉を許しませんよ
My treasure sword will not forgive irreverent words...
相手が誰でありましょうとね
No matter whom they may be from...
The one and only king of China.
（政(せい)）中華の唯一王だ
He stated that flat out!
（肆氏(しし)）
言い切った　中華の唯一王…
The one and only king of China?!
In these 500 years of war
この500年の大乱の中
there's only one king I've heard speak such reckless words.
そんな無謀な言葉を口にした王は
１人しか知りません
かつて“戦神(いくさがみ)”とまで恐れられた…
The one once feared as the God of War...
Do not speak the name of King Zhao again.
昭王(しょうおう)の名は 二度と口にするな
それが お前のためだ
For your own sake.
Please wait, my king!
（昌文君(しょうぶんくん)）お待ちを 大王…
その男の前で
昭王を語るのは危険です！
It is dangerous to speak of King Zhao in front of that man!
The God of War, King Zhao.
（政）戦神 昭王
在位55年のうち そのほとんどを
戦に投じた我が曽祖父
A man whom held a 55 year reign, most of which was devoted to war. My great grandfather...
You are not the only one who respected him as a king.
彼を王と慕っていたのは
お前だけではない
秦国中の武人が 自らの命を
差し出すほどに 忠誠を尽くした
Warriors all over the State of Qin went so far as to offer up their lives in devotion to him.
しかし 昭王が崩じて 早(は)や７年
But! King Zhao died nearly seven years ago!
王騎！ お前は 最愛の主(あるじ)を失い―
Wang Qi! You lost your most beloved master,
and you've become a hollow bird, writhing in pain, seeking for a place to land.
着地する場所を求めて
もがき苦しんでいる むなしい鳥だ
As long as you chase after King Zhao's shadow, you'll never have a place to descend to.
昭王の影を追っているかぎり
お前の降り立つ場所など ないぞ
無論 俺から お前の止まり木に
なってやる気など 毛頭ない
Of course, I do not have the least intention of becoming your perch.
もし俺と共に戦いたいと願うのなら
If you wish to fight together with me,
accept King Zhao's death and try putting your feet on the ground.
昭王の死を受け入れ
一度 地に足を着けよ
Only then will you fly across China.
中華に羽ばたくのは それからだ
Mystery Bird of Qin!
秦国の怪鳥よ！
（王騎）“中華に羽ばたく”…
Fly across Qin...
Can I reach...?
（昭王）及ばずか…
アア… やはり 中華は広かったな
China truly is vast...
わしの夢 お前に託すぞ 王騎
I'm entrusting my dream to you, Wang Qi.
フッ… ご冗談を
You kid. If I lose you, my king, I will no longer be able to fly.
大王を失っては
私は もう飛べませんよ
（昭王）
フフフッ… 情けないことを申すな
Do not speak such pitiful things.
Even if I die, the battlefield will not disappear.
わしが死んでも戦場はなくならんぞ
しかし
熱き夢を求める戦場はなくなります
But the battlefield of seeking fevered dreams will disappear.
Will it? Even in my land, there are many kings that seek China.
そうか？
わしのほかにも 中華を求める王は
いくらでもおるぞ
In words only...
口だけですよ　見れば分かります
You can tell by merely looking at them,
本気で夢を描いて
中華に恋い焦がれているかどうかは
whether or not they seriously draw out their dream and yearn lovingly for China.
A true one has a child-like glint in their eyes, like you, my king.
本物は 大王のように
瞳に 少年の輝きを宿しています
ハハハハッ…“少年”と来たか
Child-like, eh?
本気で中華を求める王など
ほかには いません
There is no other king that truly seeks all of China.
過酷な道を避けて
小競り合いを繰り返し
They avoid the more rigorous path and just repeat little quarrels over and over.
現状維持で満足する小物ばかりです
They're nothing but small fries that are satisfied with maintaining the status quo.
You're quite harsh, aren't you?
（昭王）手厳しいな
もう どこにもいませんよ
They no longer exist...
生涯を夢追いに
ささげた大王のような奇特な王は
kings like you that devote their lives to chasing a dream.
“奇特な王”か ハハハハッ…
Praiseworthy kings?
あと20年 生きられればな
If only I could live another twenty years...
I could have taken hold of my dream.
夢をつかめたやもしれぬ
王騎よ
飛ぶのは やめても 牙は磨いておれ
Wang Qi. Even if you give up on flying, keep your claws sharp.
お前ほどの武人が
地に埋もれるのは許せぬ
I cannot allow a warrior of your caliber to be buried in the ground...
Even if there's none now, a king like me
今は いなくとも―
この先 わしのような王が
再び 現れるやもしれん
may someday appear once again.
王騎よ そのときは
今以上に 大きく羽ばたくのだ
Wang Qi, when that time comes, you must fly even higher than you do now.
After King Zhao died
昭王亡きあと 数多くの王が
私を召し抱えようとしましたが
numerous kings tried to employ my services, but...
they all spoke lightly of "China" and "under the heavens".
“中華だ 天下だ”と
軽々しく語るばかりで―
There wasn't a genuine one among them.
本物は１人もいませんでした
But his young king before me... is not bad.
しかし この若王(じゃくおう)は悪くない
ンフッ…
昭王とは また違いますが
悪くないですよ
Different from King Zhao, but not bad!
In this young king's eyes, there isn't the slightest hint of the naive glint like in those of King Zhao,
この若王の目は―
中華に恋い焦がれた昭王のような
甘き輝きは微塵(みじん)もなく
the man who yearned so lovingly for China.
They firmly grasp the path to China.
しっかりと中華への道を捉えている
ンフフフッ…
若さゆえの おごりとも言えますが
One could say it's the arrogance of youth,
こんな目で中華に臨む王は
いまだかつて１人もいませんでした
a king that seeks China with eyes like these
has never before existed.
これが第31代秦王 嬴政(えいせい)ですか
So this is the 31st generation king of Qin, Ying Zheng?!
昌文君 あなたが １人で
バカ熱くなっている理由が―
Changwenjun, I feel I've begun to understand the reason why you got so foolishly heated on your own.
少しだけ分かりましたよ
（昌文君）うん？
ンフフフッ…
なかなか楽しい問答でした
That was quite an enjoyable answer.
今日は
これで引き揚げるといたしましょう
Let us leave this matter here for today.
King, I am too self-conscious to want to fight with you.
大王
私が あなたと共に戦いたいなんて
自意識過剰ですねえ
If you are going to talk big, please gain the power to match it.
そんな大口をたたくなら―
それに見合うだけの
力をつけてください
Do not be like your little brother and not know what to do with it.
弟ごときに手を焼いている場合じゃ
ありませんよ
ンフフフッ… では
Farewell.
All forces, withdraw!
全軍 撤収です
（兵士たち）はっ！
That goes for you, too, Teng.
（王騎）騰(とう)も 撤収ですよ
（騰）はっ…
Yes, my lord.
（王騎）昭王よ
King Zhao...
また 熱い時代が
来ようとしているのかもしれませぬ
Another heated age may be coming.
Damn you, Wang Qi.
王騎め…
魏興(ぎこう)を斬ったことは許し難いが
この場の時を止めたのも事実
It's difficult to forgive you for cutting down Weixing, but...
it is also true that you stopped time on this battlefield.
Now, before they can learn that Chancellor Jie has been killed
今なら 竭丞相(けつじょうしょう)が討たれたことを
知られる前に―
一気にカタをつけられる…
we can make one final push to finish this!
（信）ハァハァ…
（成蟜(せいきょう)）ハッ！
（成蟜）ヒイッ…
（肆氏）ハッ…
ヒイ～ッ！
（肆氏）成蟜さま お待ちあれ！
Lord Chengjiao! Please, wait!
What? The war's stopped.
何だ？ 戦が止まってるぞ
信！
Xin!
うん？ オオッ！ 生きてたか
Oh! You survived, huh?!
ウワッ！
Lord Chengjiao?
（兵士Ｅ）成蟜さま…
（兵士Ｆ）なぜ成蟜さまが ここに
Why is Lord Chengjiao here?
Ying Zheng! This guy is Ying Zheng!
嬴政！
こやつが嬴政だ　殺せ殺せ！
Kill him! Kill him!
What are you bastards doing?!
何をしている？ 貴様ら
さっさと殺せ！ 斬れ！
Hurry up and kill him! Cut him down!
どういうことなのだ？ これは
What is going on here...?
Chancellor Jie!
竭丞相！
バカな…
（兵士Ｇ）我々は負けたのか？
It can't be...!
We... have lost?
き… 来てみろ ゲスが！
J-Just try it, low-life!
だ… 大王である この俺が
じきじきに斬り伏せてくれるわ！
I-I, the king, am going to cut you down personally!
成蟜 お前は―
Chengjiao...
You are nothing more than a fool who mistakenly believes the fortune one was born with equates to their value.
生まれのよさが 人の価値の全てと
勘違いした ただの愚か者だ
お前には 決して王など務まらぬ！
You are unfit to be king!
You half-a-man, acting so mighty...
半端者が偉そうに…
では貴様に王が務まるというのか？
Then you're saying you're fit to be king?
半分
庶民の血を引く半端な王族の貴様が
You, a person who's blood is half of a commoner and half of the royal family, think you can rule the people?!
民を支配できるのか？
Yes.
できる
俺は認めぬぞ
I won't approve it...
純血である俺こそが民を支配し
I, who am of pure blood, will rule the people and strengthen the country!
国を強くするのだー！
曲がった教育を受けたな 成蟜
You've accepted a truly warped education, Chengjiao.
The people are not as simple as you nor I think.
俺や お前が思うほど
民は単純ではない
我ら王族に それほどの関心もない
And we royals are not of as much concern as we think.
ああ くだらねえ！
Yeah, meaningless!
俺たち底辺の人間には
誰が王かなんて 興味がないんだ！
For us humans at the base of society, who don't give a damn who the king is!
（政）
お前は高みで反り返っているだけで
民の心を知らぬ
While you were arching your back towards the heavens, you never knew of the hearts of the people...
All you did was look down on those around you!
できるのは周りを見下すことだけだ
（成蟜）ウワッ！
世を知らぬ！ 人を知らぬ！
You know nothing of the world and know nothing of the people.
That is why you are always all alone!
だから
お前は いつも ただひとり！
You are not fit to be king!
お前では 王は務まらぬ！
黙れ… 黙らぬか…
Shut up... Why don't you shut up?
秦国の王は…
The King of Qin...
The King of Qin is me!
秦国の王は 俺だー！
ウワッ！
アアーッ！
腕がー！ 血が！ 血が！
My arm! Blood! Blood!
それくらいの血が どうした？
What does such a small amount of blood matter?
For the sake of your whims,
お前の気まぐれのために
大勢の人間が ムダに血を流し
a great number of people have meaninglessly shed blood and died!
命を落としたんだぞ
（剣を捨てる音）
Do you understand that?!
分かっているのか？
き… 貴様！
よくも この俺に こんなマネを！
Y-You bastard! How dare you do this to me...!
ただで済むと思うなよ
Don't think you'll be forgiven for this!
この薄汚い庶民の女から
生まれた半端なヤツめ！
You half-man, born from a dirty commoner woman!
言いたいことは それだけか？
Is that all you have to say?!
アガガ… アガ…
Chengjiao. Learn a little of the people's pain!
成蟜 お前は少し 人の痛みを知れ！
（殴る音）
ごめんなさい… ごめんなさい…
I'm sorry!
I'm sorr... Sorry!
（殴る音）
ごめんなさい… ごめんなさい…
I'm sorry!
I'm... I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい…
（泣き声）
戦いで死んだ者たちの思いは
この何千 何万倍だ
The emotion of those that died in battle is thousands, tens of thousands times this!
勝敗が決した今 殺す値打ちもない
With victory decided, you're not worth killing.
くだらぬことで血を流し過ぎた
これ以上の流血は無用！
Too much blood has flowed for foolish things!
It's meaningless for it to happen any more!
I'll guarantee that everyone's lives will be spared, so surrender at once!
全員の命を保証してやるゆえ
直ちに投降せよ！
必要最低限の犠牲をもって
反乱の決着とする！
Let this rebellion end with the lowest number of sacrifices as possible!
（どよめき）
（兵士Ａ）い… 命を保証？
S-Spare out lives?!
Didn't you guys hear?
（信）聞こえなかったのか？
とっとと武器捨てて降伏しやがれ！
Hurry up, drop your weapons and surrender!
この戦…
This war...
has ended in our victory!
俺たちの勝利だー！
（信）お～い！
（壁(へき)）あっ…
貂(てん)！
（壁）信…
Brother Bi! Is Diao doing okay?!
壁のあんちゃん 貂の具合は？
He's fine. Anyhow, what's happening in the plaza?
大丈夫だ　それより広間のほうは？
The king, is he all right?
大王は ご無事か？
殿は？ 山の王は？
And Lord? The Mountain King?
Everything's wrapped up over there.
あっちは全部 片づいた
心配すんな　みんな無事だ
Don't worry, everyone's safe.
I see...
そうか　良かった… 良かった…
I'm so glad...
あっ そうだ… 聞いてくれ 信
Ah, right. Listen, Xin.
The truth is, Diao is...
（壁）実は 貂は… あっ 大王
Ah, my king!
大王 よくぞ ご無事で…
（政）お前たちもな
My king... I'm glad you're all right.
I'm glad you are as well.
派手な戦いだったようだな
（信）大したことねえよ
It looks like it was quite a garish battle.
It was nothin' big.
フゥ…
おっさんみてえだな
（政）フッ…
You look like an old man.
放っとけ
Lay off.
（貂）うわぁ 盛り上がってますな
It's turning into a real party.
うん？ 信たちは どこだ？
Where are Xin and the others?
Diao...
（壁）貂…
（貂）うん？
Bi!
壁！
（貂）何だよ？ こんなとこに
連れてきて… 俺 腹減ってんだけど
What're you doing, dragging me to a place like this?
I'm hungry.
（壁）
楊端和(ようたんわ)たちは 明朝 山へ帰るそうだ
Yang Duan He and the other Mountain People are going back to the mountains come morning.
帰る？ せっかく仲間になったのに
Going back?
But we finally became such good friends...
（壁）山の王とはいえ全ての部族を
掌握しているわけではないらしい
Even as Mountain King, she apparently doesn't have control over every tribe.
大王が中華に出る そのときまで
Until the king leaves for the rest of China,
勢力を
強めておくということになったのだ
she said she's going to try to strengthen her authority.
へえ…
お前も 一緒に山へ帰れ
（貂）はぁ？
You should go with them back to the mountains.
男のフリをして
１人で生きていくなんて―
Give up this life of pretending to be a boy and living on your own.
もう やめるんだ
オッ！
貂のヤツ 元気そうじゃねえか
Diao looks like he's doin' well.
（バジオウ）楊端和さまは
あの子を受け入れると決められた
Lord Yang Duan He decided to take that child in.
仲間にしてやんのか？
（バジオウ）そうだ
You're making him one of your people?
Yes.
（信）もともと山の民だもんな
I guess he's originally a Mountain Person.
クソガキだけど
面倒みてやってくれよ 隊長
He's a shitty brat, but make sure you look after him, Captain.
よう
Hey.
（政）朝には王宮を出るらしいな
I heard you're leaving the palace in the morning.
Yeah. Old man Changwenjun said he'd set up a house for me.
ああ 昌文君のおっさんが
家を用意してくれるっていうからよ
Considering your achievements, you could be a guard here in the palace.
お前の功績を考えれば―
この王宮の
衛兵くらいには してやれるぞ
ハハッ… 冗談だろう？
You've gotta be kidding. There's no way I could do a boring job like that.
そんな退屈なこと
やってられっかよ
I'm heading onto the battlefield!
俺は戦場に出る！
１コ１コ積み上げて 将軍になる！
I'll pile up achievements one by one and become a general!
お前も こっから先が大変そうだな
It sounds like you've got a rough time ahead of you, too.
（政）竭氏の勢力は残したが
弱体化は明白
Jie Shi's authority still exists, but its weakening is obvious.
呂氏(りょし)の力は ますます強大になる
Lü Shi's power will become more and more great.
だが それも
俺が執政できる年になるまでだ
But that will only last until I reach the age I can govern.
二十歳になり加冠すれば
必ず 呂氏から権力を剥ぎ取る
Once I reach age 20 and come of age, I'll definitely wrench power away from Lü Shi.
And...
そして…
I will depart for China!
俺は中華に出る
（信）そっか
Is that right?
Xin, until that time comes, be sure to rise up to meet me.
信 そのときまでには
必ず上ってこい
（信）おう
Right.
( Flag - Lü )
（呂不韋(りょふい)）そうか　鎮圧されたか
（側近）はっ…
I see.
It was suppressed, was it?
Yes, sir.
では帰るか 咸陽(かんよう)に
Then I suppose I'll return to Xianyang.
You truly did well.
（政）本当に よくやってくれた
勇猛なる山の民に 心から感謝する
I thank the brave Mountain People from the bottom of my heart.
（楊端和）戦いは始まったばかりだ
The battle has only just begun.
内外の敵の動きは
共有しておいたほうがいい
We should share the burden of looking after enemies on the inside and outside.
今後は 定期的に使いの者を送る
I'll start sending a messenger to you at fixed intervals.
I'll send my own messengers as well.
こちらからも使者を出そう
技術的な交流も深めたい
I want to deepen a practical interaction as well.
You have good eyes.
いい目をしている
中華の王になる日が楽しみだ
I look forward to the day you become king of China.
Let us meet again!
また会おう
（貂）良かったな 信
俺たちの家が もらえて
You must be glad, Xin!
We got a house!
（信）俺たちじゃねえ　俺の家だ
"We" didn't get it!
It's my house!
大体
お前 なんで こっち来てんだよ？
Anyhow, why are you coming with me?
バ～カ　お前１人になったら
メシ どうするつもりだよ？
You idiot. What're you planning to do about food if you live alone?
メシぐらい どうにだって…
Figuring out food on my own is...
あっ… なる気がしねえ
not something I think I could do.
Yeah, see?!
フフッ… ほ～ら 見ろ
だから俺が一緒に行ってやるんだよ
That's why I'm going with you.
感謝しろってんだ
（信）ケッ！ 勝手にしろ
You should be thankful!
Do whatever you want.
（貂）あっ… おい！ 昌文君が
くれた家は そっちじゃないぞ
H-Hey!
The house Changwenjun gave us isn't over there!
（信）こっちでいいんだ
ちょっと寄ってく所がある
I just have a place I wanna stop by over here.
どこだ？ ここ
（信）俺と漂(ひょう)が育った村だ
What's this place?
It's the village Piao and I grew up in.
漂って…
政の身代わりになったヤツか？
Piao...
The guy who was being Zheng's double?
ああ 今の俺があるのは―
Yeah. I'm the person I am now because I met Piao here.
この村で漂と出会ったからだ
Xin... take me... with you across the world...
（漂）
信… 俺を天下に連れていってくれ
Piao!
漂ーっ！
I've made it this far, Piao.
ここまで来たぜ 漂
I made it this far on the path we chose...
お前と俺が選んだ道を ここまで
お前は 漂と出会ったから
そこまで強くなったんだな
So you got that strong because you met Piao, huh?
Yeah.
It sure is odd...
不思議なもんだよな
（信）うん？
漂は政と出会って
その政が お前と出会って
Piao met with Zheng and then Zheng met with you...
Who could've imagined that?
そんなの誰が想像できた？
When I met you, I felt like there was a big change in my fate.
俺も お前と出会って
運命が大きく変わった気がする
いや そいつは違うな
No, that's wrong.
何がだよ？
What is?
変わったんじゃねえ
それは お前が変えたんだ
It didn't change. You changed it.
運命は切り開いて変えるもんだろう
Fate is something you cut through and change.
そっか… そうだな！
Oh... I guess so!
漂 お前との思い出は
この村に埋めてくぜ
Piao... I'm burying the memories I have with you in this village.
夢に突き進むためにな
In order to push forward towards the dream.
ウオーッ！
（貂）ウワッ！
おい！ 何だよ？ いきなり
（信）やるぞ やるぞ！
Hey! What was with that all of a sudden?!
I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna do it!
信！ 俺を置いてくな！
（信）ウオーッ！
Xin! Don't leave me behind!
こら 待て 信！ 待ちやがれ！
Hey, wait, Xin!
Wait up, dammit!
（貂）な… 何じゃ こりゃー！
Wh-What the hell is this?!
What? It's a house. Obviously.
（信）いや 家だろう どう見たって
What kinda house is this?!
これの どこが家だ！
小屋だろう これは！
This is a hut, dangit!
That cheap old man!
あのおっさん ケチりやがって
信 お前も何か言ってやれよ！
Xin, say something!
It's more than enough.
十分だ
（貂）えっ？
もともと
俺は何も持ってなかったんだからな
I started off with nothing...
And now I finally have land and a house.
それが
ついに 土地と家を手に入れた
もっと武功を上げて
土地も でっかくしていくんだ
I'll gain more military achievements
and my land will get huge!
The first thing can be a broken down shack or whatever!
最初は ボロ小屋でも何でもいいさ
これが俺たちの最初の城だ
最初の城だ…
This is out first castle!
Our first castle!
ウオーッ！ やったぞー！
We did it!
やってねえよ バカ！
（信）ウオーッ！
We didn't do anything, you idiot!
kowaresou na kokoro tsumugu youni
壊れそうな心 紡ぐように
To weave together my breaking heart
yume no kakera mitsume (No more cry)
夢のカケラ見つめ (No more cry）
I gaze at the fragments of a dream (No more crying)
me no mae ni wa tsuki ga utsushidasu
目の前には月が映し出す
The moon I see before my eyes
～♪
kono mune no yakusoku
この胸の約束
reflects this promise in my heart
namida ga nokoshita kioku sae mo
涙が残した記憶さえも
I won't turn away from my tearful memories
（信）
声が出ねえ… 何だ？ この感じは
waraiatta kako sae furimukanai
笑いあった過去さえ振り向かない
nor the past where we laughed together
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）底知れぬ笑顔をたたえ
その男は静かに ひざまずく
Voice of soul
次回 “呂不韋”
Voice of you
kanashimi nara kitto tsuyosa ni kawaru hazu
悲しみならきっと 強さに変わるはず
Sadness is sure to turn into strength
I won't cry
I won't fear
I won't stop
takaku tobeba kitto sora no mukou ni todoku
高く翔べばきっと空の向こうに届く
If I jump high enough, I'm sure I'll reach beyond the sky
Voice of mine
Yeah
Voice of soul
Preview
I can't... speak...
What is this feeling?!
He wears a smile that no one knows what is under.
That man quietly kneels down.
Lü Buwei
End
Next time,